{
  "Quiz1": [
   {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 1,
      "Question_1": "What is a specific set of rules for programming languages called?",
      "Answer": "Syntax",
      "Explanation": "Syntax defines rules to use when programming."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 2,
      "Question": "What is the most used programming language?",
      "Choice1": "Java",
      "Choice2": "Python",
      "Choice3": "C",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": "C is the most used programming language.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "TF",
      "Question_Num": 3,
      "Question": "Most programming languages today are high-level languages.",
	"choicea": "True",
       	"choiceb": "False"
	"Answer": "choicea",
      "Explanation": "Most programming languages today are high-level languages."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 4,
      "Question": "What is the first successful programming language?",
      "Choice1": "FORTRAN",
      "Choice2": "LISP",
      "Choice3": "COBOL",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "FORTRAN was the first successful programming language."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 5,
      "Question_1": "HTML is a ___________ language.",
      "Answer": "Markup",
      "Explanation": "HTML is a markup language (HyperText Markup Language)."
    },
    {
      "Type": "TF",
      "Question_Num": 6,
      "Question": "Once you learn how to code in one language, it is easier to learn others due to the similar features.",
      "choicea": "True",
      "choiceb": "False"
      "Answer": "choicea",
      "Explanation": "It is true that once you learn how to code in one language, the similar features make it easier to learn others."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 7,
      "Question": "Which of the following is not a programming language?",
      "Choice1": "Ruby on Rails",
      "Choice2": "PHP",
      "Choice3": "RAM",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": "Ruby on Rails and PHP are programming languages, while RAM is Random Access Memory."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 8,
      "Question_1": "HTML stands for?",
      "Answer": "HyperText Markup Language",
      "Explanation": "HTML is a markup language (HyperText Markup Language)."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 9,
      "Question": "Which is not a level of coding?",
      "Choice1": "High",
      "Choice2": "Medium",
      "Choice3": "Low",
      "Answer": "Choice2",
      "Explanation": "High and Low are levels of coding, making Medium the correct answer."
    },
    {
      "Type": "TF",
      "Question_Num": 10,
      "Question": "Majority projects use only one programming language.",
	  "choicea": "True",
      "choiceb": "False"
	  "Answer": "choiceb",
      "Explanation": "Majority projects use multiple programming languages."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 11,
      "Question_1": "C is a _____ level language?",
      "Answer": "Low",
      "Explanation": "C is a Low level language."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 12,
      "Question": "Which of the following is not used for web development?",
      "Choice1": "PHP",
      "Choice2": "R",
      "Choice3": "JavaScript",
      "Answer": "Choice2",
      "Explanation": "R is not used for web development."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 13,
      "Question_1": "Which type of language is easier to code in?",
      "Answer": "High-level",
      "Explanation": "High-level languages are easier to code in."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 14,
      "Question": "Which language focuses on the visual appeal of a webpage?",
      "Choice1": "HTML",
      "Choice2": "JavaScript",
      "Choice3": "CSS",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": "CSS is a language that focuses on the visual appeal of a webpage."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 15,
      "Question_1": "What does CSS stand for?",
      "Answer": "Cascading Style Sheet",
      "Explanation": "CSS stands for Cascading Style Sheet."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 16,
      "Question": "Who is known as the first computer programmer?",
      "Choice1": "Ada Lovelace",
      "Choice2": "Bill Gates",
      "Choice3": "Charles Babbage",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "Ada Lovelace is known as the first computer programmer."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 17,
      "Question": "What language does Node.js use?",
      "Choice1": "Java",
      "Choice2": "JavaScript",
      "Choice3": "HTML",
      "Answer": "Choice2",
      "Explanation": "Node.js uses the language named JavaScript."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 3,
      "Question": "There are over _______ programming languages today.",
      "Choice1": "700",
      "Choice2": "800",
      "Choice3": "900",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "There are over 700 programming languages today."
    }
  ],
  "Quiz2": [
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 1,
      "Question_1": "Who is responsible for writing a program for a computer? ",
      "Answer": "Programmers",
      "Explanation": "Those who code/write programs are called programmers."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 2,
      "Question": "Which is not a type of loop in programming",
      "Choice1": "for”,
      "Choice2": "if”,
      "Choice3": "while",
      "Answer": "Choice2",
      "Explanation": "For loops and while loops exist in programming; if is part of the if/else statement.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 3,
      "Question": "What language does Node.js use?",
      "Choice1": "Java”,
      "Choice2": "HTML”,
      "Choice3": "JavaScript",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": ".js stands for JavaScript.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 4,
      "Question_1": "What does CSS stand for?",
      "Answer": "Cascading Style Sheet",
      "Explanation": "CSS is known as Cascading Style Sheets; they are used to style the webpages."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 5,
      "Question": "Computers run on ______ code.",
      "Choice1": "primary”,
      "Choice2": "binary”,
      "Choice3": "decimal",
      "Answer": "Choice2",
      "Explanation": "We use binary code on most electronics, meaning that their basic level is formed with 0s and 1s.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 6,
      "Question_1": "Python is a _____ language",
      "Answer": "Scripting",
      "Explanation": "Python."
    },
    {
      "Type": "SC",
      "Question_Num": 7,
      "Question": "There are over _______ programming languages today.",
      "Choice1": "700",
      "Choice2": "800",
      "Choice3": "900",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "There are over 700 programming languages today."
    },
    {
      "Type": "TF",
      "Question_Num": 8,
      "Question": "Majority projects use only one programming language.",
      "choicea": "True",
      "choiceb": "False"
      "Answer": "choiceb",
      "Explanation": "Majority projects use multiple programming languages."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 9,
      "Question_1": "HTML stands for?",
      "Answer": "HyperText Markup Language",
      "Explanation": "HTML is a markup language (HyperText Markup Language)."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 10,
      "Question": "Which of the following is used for web development.",
      "Choice1": "Python”,
      "Choice2": "R”,
      "Choice3": "JavaScript",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": "JavaScript is the only option that we can use for web development, along with others like HTML and CSS.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "TF",
      "Question_Num": 11,
      "Question": "The first ever computer virus was meant to be malicious.",
	  "choicea": "True",
      "choiceb": "False"
	  "Answer": "choiceb",
      "Explanation": "The first ever computer virus was not meant to be harmful; it was an accident."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 12,
      "Question": "What is the first successful programming language?",
      "Choice1": "FORTRAN",
      "Choice2": "LISP",
      "Choice3": "COBOL",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "FORTRAN was the first successful programming language."
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 13,
      "Question": "What was the earliest programmable computer?",
      "Choice1": "FORTRAN",
      "Choice2": "The Internet",
      "Choice3": "The Analytical Engine",
      "Answer": "Choice3",
      "Explanation": "The Analytical Engine was the earliest programmable computer, developed by Charles Babbage."
    },
    {
      "Type": "Blank",
      "Question_Num": 14,
      "Question_1": "What does OOP stand for?",
      "Answer": "Object Oriented Programming",
      "Explanation": "OOP is Object Oriented Programming.”
    },
    {
      "Type": "MC",
      "Question_Num": 15,
      "Question": "Who is known as the first computer programmer?",
      "Choice1": "Ada Lovelace",
      "Choice2": "Bill Gates",
      "Choice3": "Charles Babbage",
      "Answer": "Choice1",
      "Explanation": "Ada Lovelace is known as the first computer programmer."
    }
  ]
}
